If you have also taken a policy of Adila Sun Life Insurance, then
you will
definitely get to see even the smallest videos.  I am hiding my face in the video
or changing my voice like this
because in my upcoming videos
I will say hello friends how are you?  How are
you all?  Actually the motive of making a video is
that as an Adit Bilal Sun Life
Insurance Expert as an Adit Bilal Sun
Life Insurance SME as an Adit Bilal Sun
Life Insurance Expert Product Master, the
motive of making a video is that
many customers have received a call
like your policy has been credited, you
bought a car, on that you had an
insurance of Aditya Bilal Sun Life Insurance,
you had taken the policy in 2017, you had taken the policy in 2016,
you had paid the premium,
then you did not pay, then your policy was
credited, so the bonus was generated, you
bought a motor, on that you have got a
policy of Aditya Life Insurance.
Now this is your bonus generated or you
receive a lot of calls.  You
receive many fake calls from your fraudsters
that your policy has lapsed or that
you had taken a loan earlier
or you had an Aditya
Bilsan Life Insurance loan from some other company and
they provide you with a policy number
that the policy has lapsed.  I am sharing the link.
You make the payment.  It will
become active.  You will receive your bonus amount within a month
or you will not have to make that payment.
Just share your Aadhar card and PAN card with us.
You will be activated from here.
Or you are asked to
visit the branch of Aditya Birla Sunlife
Insurance.  So in this way you neither have to make
payment nor share documents
nor visit any branch.
What do you have to do?  Aditya Birla Toll Free
Number What to do on Aditya Birla Toll Free Number
?  You have to call.  I am
mentioning the toll free number here.
Call there and what do you have to do?
You have to check from your registered mobile
number or from the mobile number which was registered before you, whether
you had any policy of Billa Sun Life
Insurance or not or whether the
policy which they have told is in your name or
not.  Okay, so you have to get both of these checked
and here I would even like to request you that you do
not have to submit any document, any amount or visit any branch,
you just have to get it verified.  What does this
do?  Fraudsters call and ask for
documents or money or if they visit the branch and
pay the money, then it becomes
fraud.  If only documents are
shared then an Aditya
Birla Sun Life Insurance policy is shared in his name.
Issue the policy.  So what I will do is
request
you all not to share any documents or any
amount without verifying it.   There is a
lot of fraud going on.  Age Adi Billa Sun
Life Insurance Expert Age Adi Billa Sun
Life Insurance SME Age Adi Billa Sun
Life Insurance Product Master I have
experience of this entire life
insurance product for one year, so
I know every small thing, which customers are
defrauded,
what happens to the customers, I know all the details,
that is why you must share this video,
definitely like the video, subscribe to this channel,
I will tell you even the smallest,
if you have taken Aditya Billa Sun Life Insurance
policy, then
you will definitely get to see the smallest video
related to auto debit, related to premium, related to
maturity, related to surrender,
small things, if the customers make mistakes,
they suffer huge losses.  So I
would like to request you to please like and
subscribe to this video.
Share it with your friends and I would
like to request you again that you should
not share any document, any amount
without verification.  Thank you Age Adi
Vilas Life Insurance Expert.  Have a great
day.  We will keep you updated on the next video.
I am hiding my face in the video or
changing my voice because
in my upcoming videos I am going to
share such videos with you that may cause
issues for me, sir.  That's why I am
hiding my face or changing my voice.  There are
some reasons why I have to face it.
I will have to face it.  So
sorry for this, sorry for changing the voice
or sorry for hiding the face.  But I will definitely
reveal my face with your support.  So
please guys support